beauty.com 2012-12-18

# Beauty.com - Cosmetics, Skin Care, Fragrances, Beauty and Makeup Tips

**TRUSTe Licensee**

Drugstore.com, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. This statement discloses the privacy practices for www.drugstore.com, including the drugstore.com Pharmacy and Beauty.com Web store. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@drugstore.com](mailto:privacy@drugstore.com).  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe here.(<http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>).

**Information We Collect**   
We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect on our Web sites to provide you with a superior shopping experience and to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions.

**Your Account**   
When you place an order, we will ask you to set up "your account," which includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. Using your account information, we will send you communications that we believe are relevant to you, including eMedalert™, newsletters and e-mails. If you prefer not to receive optional e-mails or other communications from us, you may adjust your account to prevent such communications by clicking on "subscriptions" within "your account."

If you would like to review or revise the information we have in your account, you may access such information by clicking on the "your account" link below or on any screen of our site.

**Customer Reviews**   
We are pleased to hear from our customers and welcome your comments regarding our products. We include customer reviews on our website to allow other customers to see what you think about a product. These reviews may contain personally identifiable information, such as your name, should you choose to use your first and/or last name. We also allow you the option of sharing your review anonymously by entering a “nickname” when submitting your review. To request removal of your personal information from these reviews, contact us at [privacy@drugstore.com](mailto:privacy@drugstore.com).  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Information Automatically Collected**   
We automatically receive and collect certain types of information whenever you visit our Web stores. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and Web beacons (described below) and obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Web sites. This information includes the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, geographic location as determined by your IP address, your browser software and operating system, your web server, the date and time you access our site, session information (such as download errors and page response times), information about your viewing, search and purchase history and information about the referring URL and the URL clickstream to, through, and from our Web sites. We use this information to monitor the usage and performance of our site, to enhance our customers' search and shopping experiences and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.

If you would like more information about these practices and to know your choices about not having this information used, please visit <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/opting_out.aspx>.

**Information From Third Parties**   
If we receive updated account information from third parties, we may revise your account for you so that we can efficiently process your orders, deliver your packages or otherwise communicate with you. For example, we may receive customer information from our shippers or from third parties with which we operate co-branded businesses. In addition, we may acquire customer names, e-mail addresses and mailing addresses for select mailings from third parties.

**Other Information You Provide**   
We collect additional information that you choose to give us. For example, you provide information to us when you complete surveys or sweepstakes/contest entry forms, add items to Your List™, sign up for special discounts or coupons, communicate with us by e-mail, phone or otherwise, provide product reviews, or provide alternative delivery addresses.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties  
** We protect all of your information against unauthorized access or release. We share your personal and prescription information with third parties as follows:

  * Flexible Spending Account (FSA) Purchases – When you make a purchase from the drugstore.com™ Web store of FSA-reimbursable items that will be automatically deducted from your FSA account (i.e., if you use your FSA-approved credit or debit card to make the purchase or if we have an arrangement with your FSA administrator to provide electronic substantiation on your behalf), we share with your FSA administrator a list of the FSA-eligible products you purchased, together with such account, transaction and payment information as may be requested by your FSA administrator for the purpose of substantiating and tracking your purchase. We do not share with your FSA administrator information about non-FSA items you purchase. 
  * Brand Manufacturers - We may develop programs with some of our brand manufacturers through which you may be offered special discounts or coupons on products in exchange for providing your e-mail address or completing a survey about the manufacturer's products. When you are offered such discounts or coupons in exchange for providing information (for example, giving your e-mail address or completing a survey), you will be notified that if you choose to participate, your name, e-mail address and responses will be shared with the brand manufacturer. We will share no other information.
  * Brand Partnerships - drugstore.com may partner with outside brands or vendors to fulfill orders placed through their websites. We may share your name and email address with these outside vendors or brands that refer you to drugstore.com to complete your order.
  * Agents - We may enter into agreements with other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include analyzing data; providing marketing assistance; processing credit card or debit card payments; fulfilling and delivering orders. Additionally, third party providers send promotional e-mails on our behalf to such companies' customers or present advertisements on our behalf, a function called “behavioral targeted advertising.” These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies (i) to present advertisements tailored to interests you have shown while browsing, (ii) to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before so as to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements, and (iii) to understand the patterns of people who see advertisements. In doing so, the provider collects non-personal data such as your browser type, operating system, Web sites you have visited, the time of the visits, the content you viewed, ads you viewed, and similar information. The provider may connect information about your visit on our Web site with information about your visit on other sites and tailor your advertisements based on this combined information. The companies and individuals with which we work have access only to information necessary to perform their functions. They are not allowed to use the information for any other purpose and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information. We may share non-personal, summary, or aggregate customer data with partners and other third parties. Some third party providers may not be bound by this privacy policy. Their use of third party cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies by these ad network providers may be governed by their own policy. If you desire not to have your personal information used to deliver targeted personalized advertising, you may opt-out of some companies personalized advertising services by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>
  * Business Transfers - We may buy or sell stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information is usually treated as one of the transferred business assets. Should drugstore.com, inc., or Beauty.com, Inc., or substantially all of either of their assets be sold, customer information will be one of the transferred business assets. In that event, we will post a notification on this page or send you an e-mail so that you are always aware of how we are using your information. 
  * Compliance with Law; Protection of Rights, Property or Safety - We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or legal process served on us; and/or to protect our rights and the rights of our customers; or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other policies or user agreements.
  * As You Direct - If you direct, we will release other personally identifiable information to your authorized representative, an authorized practitioner caring for you, specified marketing partners, or such other person as you may direct. At the direction of the customer and to the extent specifically authorized by law, we will release such information to other persons, including specified marketing partners. 

From time to time, we may partner with certain companies who, in conjunction with membership programs, subscription services, or rewards programs, require that we disclose purchasing or other personal information about their members who visit our Web store (for example, to earn points for purchases made on our site through links from the partner site). We will disclose only the information required to make these programs work for you and support your membership in them. In addition, we disclose this information to such companies only if you have consented first, including consent implied by your agreement to the membership or participation rules. If you do not want us to disclose that information to the strategic partner, then you must contact the partner directly.

**Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.**

**Security**   
When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card or debit card information are encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet, We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us and once we have received it. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database that is away from our Web site database so it is not connected to the Internet, to keep it safe from hackers. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Questions about the security of our website should be directed to [privacy@drugstore.com](mailto:privacy@drugstore.com).

**Cookies**   
To personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Although we do not store personal information in cookies, we do tie cookies to a customer member ID which is then used to pull personal information out of the database for identification purposes. Cookies also let us know how you found us (e.g., through a particular web site or advertisement). Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server. This information can be accessed only when you enter your name and password. If you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject our cookies, you will not be able to make purchases from our Web stores or take advantage of many of our features, such as Your List™.

**Web Beacons**   
From time to time we contract with third party companies to help us better provide relevant products, services and information to you and to help us effectively measure advertising effectiveness. Some of these companies use cookies and/or Web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs). A Web beacon is a transparent image that has been placed on a Web page and sends a signal when a user has visited that page. A Web beacon does not contain any personal information. No information that is personally identifiable to you is transmitted to the third party using the Web beacon. The third party is required to protect the privacy of the information it receives using Web beacons or cookies and is not allowed to use the information it receives for any purpose beyond what is necessary to assist us. In addition, we may use web beacons in connection with the e-mails we send to our customers, to determine whether and when the images in our e-mail were rendered (which allows us to determine whether the e-mail was opened). This information may then be aggregated and used to assess the effectiveness of our e-mail communications .

**Unsolicited E-mail (SPAM)**   

Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes "harvest" your e-mail address directly from your computer or another person's address book or even obtain your e-mail address through programs that automatically search web pages and e-mail traffic for e-mail addresses. If you opt out of receiving e-mail advertisements from drugstore.com, we may share that information with third parties in order to instruct them not to send advertisements on our behalf to you. If drugstore.com shares opt out information with a third party, we will direct such third party to use this information solely to eliminate potential recipients from any e-mails they send out on our behalf.

Please note that all e-mail that originates from us will either display the drugstore.com™ or Beauty.com™ logo (HTML e-mails) or contain the drugstore.com, inc. or Beauty.com, Inc. copyright notice (text emails). In addition, our e-mails will contain our corporate address in Bellevue, Washington. If you receive an unsolicited e-mail that you believe is connected with us in any way, please forward the e-mail (as an enclosure) [abuse@drugstore.com](mailto:abuse@drugstore.com) and we will investigate.

**Children**   
We do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use our Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Linked Web Sites**   
Our Web stores may contain links to and from other sites operated and maintained by separate companies. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites (including the Web sites of participants in our associate program) and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. The privacy policies of these sites may differ from our policy, so you should always review the privacy statement of each linked Web site you visit.

**Tell-A-Friend**   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the site. www.drugstore.com does not store this information.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, request deletion, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing us at [privacy@drugstore.com](mailto:privacy@drugstore.com).  We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

As long as your account is active, we will retain your information for the purpose of providing you with our services.  If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@drugstore.com](mailto:privacy@drugstore.com).  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Your Consent**   
By using our Web site (including through our customer service line), you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we clearly state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change.

**Your Comments**   
We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to drop us an e-mail at [privacy@drugstore.com](mailto:privacy@drugstore.com) or write us:

drugstore.com, inc.   
Privacy Officer   
411 108th Avenue NE, Suite 1400   
Bellevue, WA 98004

Last updated:  July 3, 2011

Copyright © 2011 drugstore.com, inc. All rights reserved.
